is.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy | Inside Sales

At InsideSales.com, Inc. (“ ** _InsideSales_** “, “ ** _We_** “, “ ** _Us_** “), we are committed to protecting your privacy as described below. This Privacy Policy (“ ** _Policy_** “) discloses the privacy practices for the InsideSales website and the InsideSales web applications located at www.InsideSales.com.  
Except as otherwise discussed in this Policy, this document only addresses the collection, use, and disclosure of information that we (i.e., InsideSales and its agents) collect from you on this site and the InsideSales web applications associated with this site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how this information can be accessed and updated. The use of information collected through our web applications shall be limited to the purpose of providing the services for which you have engaged us. Data stored in our Software as a Service solution by our customers is subject to the customers’ privacy policies, not ours.

Other sites that are not owned or controlled by InsideSales may have their own privacy policies that apply to those sites. In addition, certain third-party offerings that are made via the InsideSales website are subject to the terms of third-party privacy policies and the terms of this Policy shall not apply. We encourage you to ask questions, to review the privacy policies of other sites, and to be very cautious before you disclose your personally identifiable information to other sites.

For a fuller discussion of our privacy practices, please see the Frequently Asked Questions (“FAQ”) below. You are responsible for reviewing the Policy each time before using our website or providing any personally identifiable information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us via email at [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@insidesales.com). If you believe we have violated the Policy, please notify us, and we will promptly investigate and try to remedy the problem.

Listing and Links to Frequently Asked Questions

1. What information do we collect from you?  
2. Where do we collect information from you?  
3. How do we use the personally identifiable information we collect from you?  
4. Who is collecting information?  
5. With whom do we share your information?  
6. What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?  
7. How can I update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?  
8. What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?  
9. What about the privacy of visitors who are 13 and under?  
10. How does tracking technology collect, use, and distribute information?  
11. Where can I find any changes to the Privacy Policy?  
**  
Frequently Asked Questions  
**  
**1\. What information do we collect from you?**

We collect information via the website that falls into one of two categories: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is information that is used to identify you. We collect personally identifiable information whenever you voluntarily submit it to the website, including your name, email, company, mailing address, title, area of expertise, telephone number, and credit card information, plus your preferences regarding InsideSales products (collectively, “personally identifiable information”). If you apply to an open position in the “careers” section of our website, we will also ask you for your resume. Non-personally identifiable information is information that is not directly tied to a specific user, such as the number of people who visit the website from various states. As is true of most web sites, we automatically collect and store in log files, statistics and other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregated (i.e., collective) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts. Non-personally identifiable information also includes information that indirectly (i.e., combined with information collected about you off the website) could be used to identify you, but in practice is not. You have the right to access, and receive copies of, personal data held about you. This right can be exercised by contacting us at [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@insidesales.com).

**2\. Where do we collect information from you?**

_Tradeshows and Webinars:_  When you attend a tradeshow or a webinar we sponsor, we may collect personally identifiable information that we would use to later contact you.

_Software Usage_ : When you use software provided by InsideSales, we may collect and use certain personally identifiable information in order to operate and enhance the software. For example, if you use InsideSales email software with your own email client, like Gmail or Outlook, we will use your email settings and email address to send and track emails on your behalf.

_Information Downloads_ : When you download any information from our website or any of our white papers, case studies, or other materials, we may collect and use certain personally identifiable information (e.g., the information you selected, your planned use for the information, your contact information) for use by InsideSales.

_View a Video_ : Prior to your viewing a video, we may keep a record of what videos were viewed for use by InsideSales.

_Purchases_ : When you make a purchase, we keep track of what you bought, along with other personal and product information (such as payment, shipping, and warranty data).

_Newsletters & Promotional Emails_: From time to time, we may offer free electronic newsletters and promotional emails as a service to our registered users, based on a voluntary subscription. If you sign up, we will send you newsletters and emails periodically listing industry news, industry events, product information, and other promotions. You will only receive a newsletter if you have provided us with your email address.

_Webmaster Lists_ : If you are a webmaster and send us an email, we will collect your email address.

_Chat Rooms and Bulletin Boards_ : From time to time, we may make chat rooms and bulletin boards available to registered users. Please remember that postings to bulletin boards and chat rooms become public information; thus, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personally identifiable information within such forums, as it may be collected and used by third parties.

_Search Terms:_  From time to time, we may offer the ability for you to search our website for information that interests you. We may save those search terms and display certain banner ads tied to your search term.

_Online Surveys and Polling_ : We may provide you the opportunity to participate in an online survey or interactive poll on our site. If you participate, we may ask you for your contact information (such as name, shipping address, etc.) and your preferences in order to track voting.

_Epostcards_ : From time to time, we may offer you the ability to send an epostcard, or email, to your friends containing content or links to our site or to content that you think your friends would find interesting. In order to do this, we must collect the user names and email addresses of your friends. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. InsideSales stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of this feature. Your friend may contact us at [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

_Contact Information & Third-Party Data_: If you contact InsideSales by email or letter, we may keep a record of your personal correspondence. Thus, if you report a problem with our website, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. Moreover, if you contact us through our feedback area, we require your name and email address in order to send you a reply. Additionally, if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our site, we may keep the information in a file specific to you.

_Browsing_ : An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers and ad servers to identify your computer. InsideSales collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to be served on our site, to report aggregated information to our advertisers, for security purposes, and to monitor the level of activity on our site.

**3\. How do we use the information we collect from you?**

_Operation of the Website and Email_ : The information we collect from you is used to operate and enhance our website. We collect personally identifiable information in order to learn more about you so we can provide you with content, products, and advertising that you are more likely to find interesting. We may combine this with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service. We also use registered user information to contact users when necessary and to send promotional emails.

_Merchants_ : Except as disclosed in this Policy, we will not share personally identifiable information about our users with other merchants and third parties without your permission.

_Emails_ : We will send registered users email containing information we think they will find interesting, such as information about news, new products and services from our selected partners. It is our policy not to send messages to members who have asked us not to do so. By using our website, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you have the ability to opt out. Please see the “What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?” section below.

_Testimonials:_  We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com).

**4\. Who is collecting information?**

_Co-branded Services_ : Some website services are offered in conjunction with a partner company. In order to provide a co-branded service to you, it is necessary for us to share your personally identifiable information with our partner company. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using our service. Also, when you send an email from our website, our third-party email provider will drop a cookie on your computer that will be used to track page views and tie them to people who have sent emails or who have filled out web forms.

_Promotions, Contests, and Sweepstakes_ : Promotions that run on the website may be sponsored by InsideSales and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer (for example, in the terms and conditions of a contest). You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared.

_Links and Ads to Third-Party Sites_ : Please be aware that sites on our website may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linked to our website are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information. Additionally, other companies or ad servers that place advertising on our website may collect information about you through the use of cookies or clear GIFs when you view or click on their advertising. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect.

_Social Media Widgets:_  Our Web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, links to our social media presence on various sites and widgets, such as the share this button or other mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

_Log-in APIs:_  You can log in to the customer support area of our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and may provide you the option to share certain personally identifiable information or post information about your activities on this web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

_Framing/Windows to Third-Party Sites_ : In addition to providing links to other websites, we sometimes window third-party sites for your convenience. If you click to learn more information, a window or frame containing the third party’s site may appear. Any time you are in a window (unless the window is another part of the InsideSales website), you should assume your personally identifiable information is being collected, used, and disclosed in accordance with the windowed site’s policies.

_Chat Rooms and Bulletin Boards_ : Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you participate in chat rooms or message boards, your user name will be displayed with your comment or posting. Information you provide while using services such as website chat rooms and bulletin boards is available for all to see; discretion should be used in disclosing personally identifiable information within such forums, as it may be collected by third parties. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personally identifiable information to others.

_Surveys and Polling_ : From time to time, we may use a third party to conduct surveys about our website or polls about a particular issue. If we do, we will either tell you in advance who that third party is, or obtain their promise that personally identifiable information will not be used or further shared with anyone outside of InsideSales. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information.

**5\. With whom do we share your information?**

We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

_Merchants_ : Other than as disclosed in this Policy or with your permission, we will not share your personally identifiable information with merchants. If you do give permission to share your information, you should know that once your personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, we cannot control how it is used or who else it may be shared with.

_Partners/Sponsors_ : We may work with partners or sponsors provide access to content or events, both physical and virtual. When you access such content or events, we may share your personally identifiable information with the associated partners or sponsors.

_Fulfillment_ : Some online activities necessarily lead to disclosure of your personally identifiable information to third parties, such as when you include your name and email address in an email to a third party or when you order merchandise in the shopping areas of our website for direct shipment to you. For example, in order to fulfill certain product orders, we must share your information with the product manufacturer, payment processor (e.g., credit card companies), and shippers.

_Agents/Service Providers_ : We also may share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the purposes of providing services to our website or to InsideSales itself, such as administering customer support and providing support tools to our users. These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information  _only as necessary to provide_  these services to us.

_Data Analysis Agents_ : The information collected through the website may be provided to an outside company for the purpose of analysis. This analysis is to help us to improve our sites and services to you, and to notify you of special offers that may be of interest to you.

_Chat Profile, Chat Rooms, and Bulletin Boards_ : It is important to note that information you provide as part of your chat profile is not confidential and is accessible by the public. Similarly, any information you provide in chat rooms, message boards, or other public forums is not confidential. For such activities, a separate warning may not be provided. Your choice to disclose personally identifiable information in these cases is voluntary.

_Ad servers and Advertisers_ : We may disclose aggregated information about our website to third parties, including informing our advertisers whether their advertisement was effective. These third parties will have permission to use their cookies’ identification numbers to serve ads on our site and to collect aggregated information to create statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third-party advertisers. However, these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

_Compliance with Service of Legal Process or Law Enforcement_ : Although it is unlikely, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. If we receive such a request, without prior notice to you we will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order subpoena, to comply with bankruptcy proceedings, to investigate hacking attempts, to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation or other similar legal processes. If we receive a subpoena as part of third-party civil litigation, we will attempt to provide you with electronic notice (i.e., via email) fourteen (14) days prior to disclosure of personally identifiable information. Moreover, we may release account information without notice to you when we in good faith believe such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Service Agreement or to protect the rights, property, computer security, and safety of our website, our users, or others.

_Sale of the Company_ : You agree that we may assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your name, address, email address, member name, and any other personally identifiable information collected by us via the website in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of the assets or stock of InsideSales or its affiliated entities. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

**6\. What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?**

_Information You Provide_ : We collect any information you enter on the InsideSales web site. You may choose not to provide certain information, though it may impact your ability to utilize certain features of the site.

_Email and Promotional Mailings_ : We may from time to time send you email or other communications regarding our products and services. If you do not wish to receive these promotional mailings, the website provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving these communications by following the opt-out instructions in the email or sending an email to[privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com). After that, InsideSales users will not receive future communications or mailings.

**7\. How can I update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?**

_Website Services_ : Upon request, InsideSales will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. InsideSales provides you with a limited ability to access and edit the personally identifiable information you have provided to us. Following registration you can review, change, or delete the information you have submitted. We encourage you to update your information promptly if it changes. To change, modify, or delete the information you previously provided you send an email to [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com), or contact us at 866-342-5370 and specify what you want to have done. We will respond to your request to access within a reasonable timeframe.

_Chat and Bulletin Board Postings_ : To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at[privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

_No Comprehensive Deletions_ : We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove if that information is necessary to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, or enforce our Terms of Service Agreement. Except as noted, upon request we will delete your information from our databases.

**8\. What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**

You can be assured that your personal and account information is reasonably secure on our website. We employ encryption technology (SSL) in all parts of our website that require you to provide your login credentials, financial or credit card information. The personally identifiable information we collect is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Credit card information is encrypted. All the information we collect and store is protected by our firewall. Also, any information we store at our business is kept physically secure, and only designated employees may obtain access to it. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.

While we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

We cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be inadvertently disclosed to third parties. We may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. If we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement, or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. If you have any other questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at[privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com).

**9\. What about the privacy of visitors who are 13 and under?**

If you are under the age of 13, you do not have permission to use our website. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personally identifiably information about users who are under the age of 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 13 years of age and believe they have disclosed personally identifiable information to this website, please contact us at [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com) so that we may delete the minor’s information.

**10\. Tracking Technologies and how they collect, use, and distribute information?**

_Tracking Technologies:_  technologies such as cookies or similar technologies are used by InsideSales and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or site optimization service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for marketing purposes, for our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference) and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or customizable areas of the site, such as message boards and chat rooms of our site, may be limited.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content, information, and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 and Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here:<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

_Advertisements_ : We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies, which we do not control, to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking[here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) ) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**11\. Where can I find any changes to the Privacy Policy?**

This Policy was implemented on and is effective immediately. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, you should send us an email opting out of it at [privacy@InsideSales.com](mailto:privacy@InsideSales.com) and we will reluctantly cancel your account privileges and remove your data (subject to the limitations described above). If we make changes to any terms or conditions of the Policy, the changes will be incorporated into this document so you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Policy. Continued use of our website after any modifications to this Policy shall constitute your consent to such modifications.

**Policy of Terminating Privileges for Infringement; Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement**

Pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512 as amended by Title II of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, InsideSales.com, Inc. (“InsideSales”), will terminate the account of any subscriber who uses his or her account privileges to unlawfully transmit copyrighted material without a license, valid defense or fair use privilege to do so. After proper notification by the copyright holder or its agent to InsideSales and later confirmation through court order or an admission by the subscriber that an account has been an instrument of unlawful infringement, InsideSales will terminate the infringing subscriber’s account. InsideSales may also in its sole discretion decide to terminate a subscriber’s account privileges prior to that time if it has good faith belief that infringement has in fact occurred. In addition, pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512(c), InsideSales has implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed infringements and for processing such claims in accordance with the Act. InsideSales respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same.

Any written notice describing the infringing activity must include the following information:

1\. an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;

2\. a description of the allegedly infringing work or material;

3\. a description of where the allegedly infringing material is located on the site;

4\. information reasonably sufficient to allow us to contact you, such as your address, telephone number, and email address;

5\. a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use of the material is not authorized by the copyright or other proprietary right owner, its agent, or the law; and

6\. a statement by you that the above information in your notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

**12\. Contact Us.**

**InsideSales.com Inc**  
1712 South East Bay Boulevard  
Suite 100  
Provo, Utah 84606

Call us at:

(888) 203-3761

E-mail us at:

**Information Related to Data Collected through the InsideSales Services**

InsideSales acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. InsideSales collects and processes 3rd party personally identifiable information under the direction of our customers. We have no ownership of this information or any direct relationship with individuals whose personally identifiable information may be processed as part of providing our Service.

An individual who seeks access, who seeks to correct, amend, delete inaccurate data or withdraw consent to further contact should direct his/her query to the InsideSales customer they interact with directly (the data controller). If an InsideSales customer requests that we remove personally identifiable information on their behalf, we will respond to their request within 30 days.

InsideSales will retain personally identifiable information we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide services and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Information for those Outside the United States**

_EU – U.S. and Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield_  
For EU and Swiss citizens, InsideSales complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. InsideSales has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit  
<https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

InsideSales commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact us at [privacy@insidesales.com](mailto:privacy@insidesales.com).

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>. If your complaint remains unresolved, you may have the option of engaging in binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Panel.

If InsideSales transfers personal information received under the Privacy Shield to a third party, the third party’s access, use, and disclosure of the personal information must also be in compliance with our Privacy Shield obligations, and we will remain liable under the Privacy Shield for any failure to do so by the third party unless we can prove we are not responsible for the damage.

InsideSales’ commitments under the Privacy Shield are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission. InsideSales may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
